kiz10.com 2019-08-29

# Privacy at Kiz10 - KIZ

### PRIVACY KIZ10

Kiz10® is committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an online privacy policy that guides how we collect, store, and use information collected about you online. 

**What information does Kiz10.com collect?**  
Kiz10® may request and/or collect non-private information from you when you use Kiz10.com and/or register. For the protection of your privacy, we ask that you avoid sending us any and all personally identifiable information. 

**Privacy and cookies policy contents**  
Introduction: commitment to privacy; document applies to controlled personal data; consent to use of cookies; website privacy controls; data controller name.  
How we use your personal data: introduction to categories, purposes and legal bases of processing; processing of usage data; processing of account data; processing of profile data; processing of service data; processing of publication data; processing of enquiry data; processing of customer relationship data; processing of transaction data; processing of notification data; processing of correspondence data; processing of other data; processing for legal claims; processing for risk management; general purposes of processing personal data; disclosure of third party personal data.  
Automated decision-making: personal data used in automated decisions; logic involved in automated decisions; significance of automated decisions.  
Providing your personal data to others: intra-group disclosures of personal data; disclosure of personal data to insurers etc; disclosures of personal data to subcontractors; disclosure of personal data to payment services providers; disclosure of personal data to third party suppliers; disclosure of personal data necessary for legal compliance etc.  
International transfers of your personal data: introduction to international personal data transfers; international transfers within business; international transfers to hosting services provider; international transfers to subcontractors; publication of personal data on internet.  
Retaining and deleting personal data: data retention introduction; personal data retention default rule; personal data retention specific rules; personal data retention criteria; personal data deletion exception.  
Security of personal data: appropriate technical and organisational security measures; personal data stored on secure servers and computers; encrypted storage of personal data; security of server-browser communications; unencrypted data sent over internet is insecure; password security.  
Amendments: amendment by publication; check for changes to policy; notification of changes to policy.  
Your rights: introduction to data subject rights summaries; list of data subject rights; summary of right to access personal data; summary of right to rectification of personal data; summary to right to erasure of personal data; summary of right to restrict processing of personal data; summary of right to object to processing of personal data; summary of right to object to processing of personal data for direct marketing; summary of right to object to processing of personal data for research purposes; summary of right to personal data portability; summary of right to complain to data protection supervisory authority; summary of right to withdraw consent to personal data processing; exercise of data subject rights.  
Third party websites: hyperlinks to third party websites; no responsibility for third party privacy policies.  
Personal data of children: website targeted at persons over specified age; deleting personal data of children.  
Updating information: correcting or updating personal information.  
Acting as a data processor: acting as a data processor; not applicable as data processor.  
About cookies: what are cookies?; persistent and session cookies; cookies and personal information.  
Cookies that we use: purposes for which cookies are used (including shopping cart).  
Cookies used by our service providers: use of cookies by services providers; google Analytics cookies; google AdSense cookies; service provider cookies (generic).  
Managing cookies: how to manage cookies; negative impact of blocking cookies; effects on website use of blocking cookies.  
Cookie preferences: managing cookie preferences.  
Our details: website operator name; company registration details; place of business; contact information.  
Data protection registration: registered with ICO; data protection registration number.  
Representative within the European Union: identity and contact details of representative of data controller.  
Data protection officer: data protection officer contact details.  

**Cookies**  
Kiz10® may use cookies to improve the use of our websites. A "cookie" is a small file that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. We do not use cookies to store personally identifiable information. Additionally, you can find more information on cookies in www.all acerca cookies.org. 

**IP Addresses**  
Kiz10® may collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. 

**Log Files**  
Other non-personal information collected by Kiz10 is in the form of logs - files that record website activity, including how many "hits" a particular web page is getting (a.k.a., "click-through data"). For example, log file entries are generated every time a visitor clicks the "Home" icon on our site. These entries enable Kiz10 to assess overall site activity, and improve the general user experience. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain information about your system such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer) and the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS). 

**Linking to third party sites**  
Kiz10® may provide links from our Web sites to third party Web sites and we encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information to them. Kiz10 assumes no responsibility for the content found on third party websites linked from Kiz10.com. Kiz10 hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site. 

**Advertisements on Kiz10**  
Kiz10® permits the use of advertising on Kiz10.com by third party advertisers. Some advertising partners may use cookies or similar technologies to better measure campaign effectiveness, target future campaigns and deliver a more targeted experience to users. Advertisers must comply with personal data guidelines, including the Data Protection Act 1998, to ensure our users� personal data is protected. Additionally, all advertisers are instructed by Kiz10 not to display ads with sexual, violent or drug & alcohol related themes. Should you find an inappropriate or offensive advertisement on Kiz10, please notify us by emailing [aguadacelia888@gmail.com](mailto:aguadacelia888@gmail.com). Additionally, third parties may collect certain types of information about your visits to Kiz10, including interaction with content on Kiz10. 

**Types of cookies**  
While visitors may kiz10.com the following cookies on your computer are introduced: 

**Session Cookies**  
These cookies last the same as your visit. They are destroyed when you close your browser or go outside kiz10.com. Information obtained through these cookies, used to analyze traffic patterns on the web and provide the services we offer through it. 

**permanent cookies**  
These cookies are enabled on your first visit to kiz10.com. They are cookies that are stored on the user's device and retrieve information that allow navigation on the next visit. They have an expiration date, but this expands beyond the end of the session. These cookies enable us to personalize your visits, through their preferences (for example, country and language). 

**google Analytics**  
kiz10.com uses Gooble Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. ( "Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer and allow an analysis of the use made of the web. The information generated by cookies on your use of this website is transmitted and stored on a Google server in the US If the anonimaci�n IP is activated on this website, Google shortens your IP address within member states of the European Union or other states which have ratified the agreement on the European Economic Area previously. Only in exceptional cases the full IP address will be transmitted to a Google server in the US and it is shortened there. By order of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to analyze your use of it, in order to compile reports on the activities of the website and provide other services related to the use of the web and the use of Internet operator. The IP address transmitted by your browser through Google Analytics not be associated with other data from Google. You can prevent the installation of cookies if configured in your browser, but please note that in this case, you might be able to not use all features of this website. Visitors can disable the use we make of Analytics by visiting Google Analytics Opt-out page.   
More about google Analytics [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2700409?hl=es)

**Google Adsense**  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on kiz10.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. kiz10.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. kiz10.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsersrespective websites.   
More about google policies [here](https://www.google.com/intl/es/policies/privacy/partners/)  
**Third Party Cookies**

**Facebook**  
Our website contains references (links) to external social network called Facebook. This website is managed exclusively by Facebook Inc. Within kiz10.com, these references are recognized by the Facebook logo or symbol "Like". Clicking on these references, Facebook plugins are activated and the browser will create a direct connection with the Facebook servers. If during your visit to our site, you click on the references and are connected to Facebook with your personal account, it will be transmitted to Facebook the information that you visited our website. This information is transmitted to Facebook and the company saves. To avoid this, you have to disconnect from Facebook before clicking on the reference. The functions assigned to the reference of Facebook, especially the transmission of information and user data are not triggered by the visit to our site, but clicking on the appropriate reference. The purpose and dimensions of data collection by Facebook, as well as processing and use of data within the company, and the corresponding right and possibility of adjusting them to protect their privacy, are governed by policy to use Facebook data (//es-es.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php). 

**Twitter**  
kiz10.com Twitter uses cookies. These cookies are enabled by a plugin of Twitter on the home page kiz10.com Most cookies are enabled Twitter if you logged into your Twitter account. Twitter uses the information collected for analytical purposes and to offer tailored content based on your interests. For example, you people will suggest who to follow on Twitter. The content tailored just stored with the ID of the browser cookie and separated from other data as the Twitter widget information visit pages. You can see the privacy policy of Twitter in twitter.com/privacy. And the information and deactivation of content personalization: support.twitter.com/articles/20169421. 

**google Plus**  
kiz10.com uses cookies from Google Plus. These cookies are enabled by a button to share Google +1. Allow content sharing website kiz10.com contacts with your Google Plus network. Most of these cookies are enabled if you are logged into your Google account. You can see the privacy policy of Google in www.google.com/intl/es/policies/privacy. Managing cookies If you want to delete any cookies stored on your computer or block cookies that collect information about your browsing patterns on the website, you can make removing your existing cookies and / or changing the privacy preferences of your browser (the process it must continue to be different in each browser). For more information on how to disable cookies or how to change your privacy options, visit www.allaboutcookies.org. The Help function of your browser should tell you how to perform this process. 

**General**  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the Kiz10.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance. We hope you have a great experience on Kiz10®. Feel free to approach us on [aguadacelia888@gmail.com](mailto:aguadacelia888@gmail.com). 

We are commited to safeguarding the privacy of our visitors, this policy establish how we will treat your personal information.

(1)Which information is collected? We can collect, store and use following kinds of personal data.

(a) Information about your computer and your visits and the use of this Website (including IP address, geographical location, kind of browser, referral source, length of the visit and number of page views);

(b) Information that you provide with the purpose of register with us (including personal data and e-mail address.)

(c) Information that you provide with the purpose of subscribing to our Web services, e-mail notifications and newsletters (including your personal data and e-mail address)

(d) any other information that you decide to send us.

(2)Cookies. A cookie consist on the information sent by a web server that is stored by a browser.  Information is sent back to the server each time the browser requests  a web from the server. This allows the server to identify and track the web browser. We may use session cookies and persistent cookies. We will use session cookies to: track you  while you browse the web,  We will use persistent cookies to : allow uor website  to recognise you when you visit us and store data of your latest gaming sessions. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer once browser is closed. Persistent cookies will be stored in your computer until they are deleted or reach an expiry date. We use Google Analytics to analize the use of this website. Google analytics generates statistical and other type information about the use of the website through the use of cookies stored in customers(users) computers.

Generated information in relation to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will sotre this information.

Google's privacy policy is available in :  [ //www.google.com/privacypolicy.html](https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html).

Our advertisers and payment services providers  could also send you cookies. Most of the browsers allow you to refuse cookies. (For example, on Internet Explorer, you can refuse all the cookies by clicking in 'Tools', 'Internet Options', 'Privacy' and selecting the option 'Block all cookies' using the scroll selector. However, this will have a negative impact in the use of a lot of websites.

(3) Use of personal data. Personal data sent to this website will be used for the purposes specified  in this privacy policy or en relevant parts of the web. We may use your informatio to:

(a) administer the website

(b) improve your browsing experience customizing the website

(c) allow the use of available services of this website

(d) send your goods purchased through the website and provide you the services acquired in the ebsite

(f) sending of General Commercial comunications

(g) Send email notifications that you have specifically requested.

(h) Send our  newsletter and games upgrades, marketing communications related to our business or third parties that have been carefully selected  and we think may be of interest for you, by post( where you have consented for this) or by email or similar technology. (you can contact us in any moment if you no longer want to receive the marketing communications)

(i) Provide third parties with statistical information about or customers(userS), but this information won't be used to  identify an individual user

(j) Listen to your queries and your complains about this website. When you send us personal information for publication in our website, such information will be pusblished and used according to the license you grant us. We won't provide your personal information to third parties with a direct marketing purpose  without your explicit consent.

(4) Disclosure, We may reveal your information to [ any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors ] as deemed appropiate for the purposes set in this privacy policy. Besides, we may disclose your information:

(a) to the extent  we are required to do so by law;

(b) In relation with any legal procedure or posible legal procedures.

(c) with the purpose to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights ( including providing information to others to fraud prevention and credit risk reduction) and (d) to the purchaser ( or potential purchaser)  of any business or asset we are selling ( or contemplate selling) . We won't provide your information to third parties except provided in this privacy policy.

(5) International data transfers. Information we collect may be stored, procesed and transfered between any of the countries in which we work in order to use the information according to this privacy policy. If you are in the  European Economic Area,(EEA), information you provide, may be transferred to countries( including U.S, Japan and other countries) which  don't have data protection laws  equivalent to those are valid in the EEA, Besides, the personal information you provide for publication on the website, will be published on the Interner and may be available through the Internet in whole world. You expressly accepts mentioned personal data transfers.

(6) Personal data safety. We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to avoid the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information that you provide to our safe server (protected by password and firewall) . OF course, data transmission through  the Internet is inherently unsecure, and we can guarantee the security of data submitted through the Internet. You are resposible to mantaint the confidentiality of your password and user data. We won't ask for your password.

(7) Policy amendments. We may update this privacy policy ocassionally by posting a new version in our website. You should visit this page from time to time to ensure your are satisfied with the changes.

(8) Your rights. You will be able to  request that we provide you any personal information we have about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a tax (currently fixed in 10 pounds). You will be able to request us for not process your personal information by email for marketing purposes in any moment. ( In practice,  usually  is that you are agree in advance with our use of your personal information for commercial purposes, or that we provide you the chance to exclude the use of your data with marketing purposes)

(9) Third parties websites. Website contains links to other websites. We are not resposibles of privacy policies or practices of third parties websites.

(10) Updating Information. Please, kindly let us know if your personal information we have collected needs to be amended or updated.

*                    Contact. If you have some question about this privacy policy or your personal data treatment, please, contact us through the Contact Form. Google, as associated provider, use cookies to publish announcements in our website. Use of Google's DART cookie, allows to serve announcements(advertisements)  to our users based on their visit to our site and others sites on the internet. Users can disable the use oDART cookie through the announcement and the content network privacy policy.
